Resume

TOMOYUKI KASHIRO

Front-end Engineer

Birth Date 30 / 04 / 1985

Languages Japanese(native), English(conversational)

Nationality Japan

Website http://tomoyukikashiro.me

Github https://github.com/kashiro

Email <u>ksrtmyk@gmail.com</u>



Summary

I am a front-end engineer developing website and web applications for six years.

I am learning back-end programs such as Ruby (Rails) currently. In addition to development work, I have extensive experience in managing projects as a project manager.

Experience

2008

2008 - 2010

Java Engineer

Rakuten, Inc.

- Developed Ecommerce recommendation and ranking system utilizing Java and Perl
- Managed API application with memcached and hadoop
- Fixed bugs and maintained the site
- · Managed projects with the business department

2010

2010 - 2012

Front-end Engineer

Rakuten, Inc.

- Worked in front-end development using standards based on HTML5 and CSS3 working with jQuery/jQuery mobile
- · Created Javascript coding guideline and reviewed codes
- Spearheaded adoption of new principles such as responsive design and mobile first
- Refined and iterated page speed by using server settings, cache server and front-end tool (minified source)

http://127.0.0.1:9000/ 1/2 ページ

2012

2012 - 2014

Front-end Engineer

KAYAC, Inc.

- · Managed projects with designer and backend programmer
- Developed UI/UX with client and designer via prototyping (bootstrap, paper prototype)
- Developed project goal and its tactics with client (UI/UX and Measurement)
- Developed web application and campaign sites utilizing standards based on HTML5 and CSS3 and featured libraries such as AngularJS, Sencha Touch, and BackboneJS
- Spearheaded teaching of front-end web security within the team

2015

2015 -

Web Developer

Freelance

- Especially good at developing E-commerce web application.
- Front-end Developer but developed server-side too using Ruby on Rails.
- Currently use Ruby on Rails and AngularJS.

Skills

Development Language		Framework, Library		Tools	
		jQuery	****	Heroku	***
HTML5	****	Sencha Touch	****	GitHub	****
CSS3	****	AngularJS	****	Google Analytics	****
JavaScript	****	Sass (SCSS)	****	Photoshop (slicing image) Travis ci Sketch3 app (slicing image)	****
Ruby	****	Jade	****		
NodeJS	***	Ruby on Rails	****		****
		Grunt / bower / Yeoman	****		****
		karma / sinon / mocha	****		

Education

2004

2004 - 2008

Sociology

TOYO UNIVERSITY

I majored in Sociology to pursue a career as PR. However, I realized the impact of the Internet and have started to study skills such as HTML and CSS.

http://127.0.0.1:9000/